roadmunk.com 2019-03-18

# Privacy Policy | Roadmapping Software | Roadmunk

#### LAST MODIFIED: MAY 25, 2018

## Privacy Policy

At Roadmunk Inc. (“Roadmunk”), we are committed to maintaining the confidentiality and security of any personal information about our users. Your privacy is always at the top of our priorities, and we are focused on protecting it from unauthorized access. This Privacy & Security Policy supplements our Terms and Conditions and spells out how we collect, use, and disclose of information from or about you through our website [www.roadmunk.com](http://www.roadmunk.com/) and the Roadmunk service.

Users can access the Roadmunk service (the “Service”) via our website [www.roadmunk.com](http://www.roadmunk.com/ "Go to roadmunk.com"), applications on Devices, APIs, and third-parties. A “Device” is any device used to access the Roadmunk Service, including without limitation a computer, mobile phone, tablet, or other electronic device. By using our Service you are consenting to the collection, transfer, processing, storage, disclosure and other uses described in this Privacy & Security Policy. The use of information collected through our service shall be limited to the purpose of providing the service for which the Roadmunk customer (“Customer”) has engaged Roadmunk.

### The Information We Collect And Store

Roadmunk employees are prohibited from viewing the content of the data you import into your Roadmunk account, except as provided in this Privacy & Security Policy. Of course, in the case that you request our help to resolve your support issues relating to that data, and only after receiving your permission, Roadmunk employees may access the relevant data.

We may collect and store the following information when running the Roadmunk Service:

#### **Information You Provide**

When you register for an account, we securely collect some personal information, such as your name, phone number, credit card or other billing information, email address, and business postal addresses.

#### **Your Data and Other Information About You**

With your permission (which you grant by signing up for or begin using our Service), Roadmunk collects and stores information you provide or that we collect in order to administer our Services and/or as otherwise described in this Privacy & Security Policy and in our Terms and Conditions.

#### **Log Data**

When you use the Service, we automatically collect certain information from your Device, its software, and your activity using the Services. This may include, for example (but without limitation), the Device's Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, the web page visited before or after you came to our website, information you search for on our website, locale preferences, identification numbers associated with your Devices, your mobile carrier, date and time stamps associated with transactions, system configuration information, metadata, and interactions with the Service.

#### **Cookies**

We also use “cookies” to collect information and provide and improve our Services. A cookie is a small file that we transfer to your Device. We may use “persistent cookies” to save your registration ID and login password for future logins to the Service. We may use “session ID cookies” to enable certain features of the Service, to better understand how you interact with the Service, to monitor aggregate usage and web traffic routing on the Service, and to enable third-party vendors, including Google, to serve ads based on someone's past visits to our website. This also enables third-party vendors, including Google, to show our ads on sites across the internet. You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all aspects of the Service.

Our affiliates use cookies to make it easier for us to gather analytics about site usage and to help us provide interactive support for our users. The use of cookies by our affiliates is not covered by our privacy policy. We do not have access or control over these cookies.

#### **How can I control cookies?**

You can set or amend your web browser controls to accept or refuse cookies. If you choose to reject cookies, you may still use our Websites and/or App and/or platform though your access to some functionality and areas may be restricted. As the means by which you can refuse cookies through your web browser controls vary from browser-to-browser, you should visit your browser's help menu for more information. In addition, most advertising networks offer you a way to opt out of targeted advertising. If you would like to find out more information, please visit <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/> or [http://www.youronlinechoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/)

#### **Widgets**

Our website includes social media features, such as the Facebook Like button and widgets, such as the “Share This” button for Twitter and LinkedIn. These features may collect your IP address and the page you are visiting on our site, and they may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

### How We Use Personal Information

#### **Personal Information**

In the course of using the Service, we may collect or otherwise obtain information that can be used to contact or identify you (“Personal Information”). Personal Information is or may be used: (i) to provide and improve our Service, (ii) to administer your use of the Service, (iii) to recommend follow-up reminders, assign tasks, or personalize the service, and (iv) to provide or offer software updates and product announcements. If you no longer wish to receive communications from us that are not required for the Service, please follow the "unsubscribe" instructions provided in any of those communications, or update your account settings information.

#### **Analytics**

We also collect some information (ourselves or using third party services) that requires using logging and cookies, such as IP address, which can sometimes be correlated with Personal Information. We use this information for the above purposes and to monitor and analyze use of the Service, for the Service's technical administration, to increase our Service's functionality and user-friendliness, to verify users have the authorization needed for the Service to process their requests, and for advertising purposes. As of the date this policy went into effect, we use Google Analytics. Visitors can opt out of Google's use of cookies for advertising purposes by visiting [Google's Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads "Google's Ads Settings"). To learn more about the privacy policy of Google Analytics, [click here](http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html "Google Analytics Privacy Policy"). To learn how to opt out of that service, [click here.](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout "Opt out of Google Analytics")

### Information Sharing and Disclosure by Us

#### **No Sale of Personal Information**

We do not sell Personal Information to third parties.

#### **Service Providers, Business Partners and Others.**

We may use certain trusted third-party companies and individuals to help us provide, analyze, and improve the Service (including but not limited to data storage, maintenance services, database management, web analytics, payment processing, and improvement of the Service's features). These third parties may have access to your information for purposes of performing these tasks on our behalf and under obligations similar to those in this Privacy Policy. As of the date this policy went into effect, we use Amazon's S3 storage service to store some of your information (for example, your files). You can find more information on Amazon's data security from the [S3 site.](https://aws.amazon.com/security/ "AWS Security")

#### **Third-Party Applications**

As of the date this policy went into effect, Roadmunk has never and will not share your information with a third-party application. In the future, with your consent, we may share your information with a third-party application (for example when you choose to access our Services through such an application). We are not responsible for what those parties do with your information, so you should make sure you trust the application and that it has a privacy policy that is acceptable to you.

#### **Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement Requests; Protection of Roadmunk's Rights**

We may disclose to third parties data stored in your Roadmunk account and information about you that we collect when we have a good faith belief that disclosure is reasonably necessary to (a) comply with a law, regulation, or compulsory legal request, such as to comply with a subpoena; (b) protect the safety of any person from death or serious bodily injury; (c) prevent fraud or abuse of Roadmunk or its users; or (d) to protect Roadmunk's rights. If we provide any data stored in your Roadmunk account to a law enforcement agency, we will remove Roadmunk's encryption from the information before providing it to law enforcement.

#### **Business Transfers**

If we are involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, your information may be transferred as part of that transaction, but we will notify you (for example, via email, sign in notification, and/or a prominent notice on our website) if that happens or if your information otherwise becomes subject to a different privacy policy in lieu of this one. We will also notify you of choices you may have regarding the information.

#### **Changing or Deleting Your Information**

If you are a registered user, you may review, update, correct, or delete certain Personal Information provided in your registration or account profile by changing your account settings. If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our Service, you may update or delete it by making the change in your account settings, although (in some cases) we may retain copies of your information if required by law, to protect our rights, or if it is not technically reasonably feasible to remove it. For questions about your Personal Information on our Service, please contact [support@roadmunk.com](mailto:support@roadmunk.com?Subject=Support%20Case "Contact Support"). We will respond to your inquiry within 7 business days.

#### **Data Retention**

Our intention is to retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you with the Services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you Services, you may delete your account. We may retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements and rights, or if it is not technically reasonably feasible to remove it. Consistent with these requirements, we will try to delete your information quickly upon request. Please note, however, that there might be latency in deleting information from our servers and backed-up versions might exist after deletion. In addition, we do not delete information from our servers files if you have that information in common with other users.

#### **Choice/Opt-Out**

You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails, or you can contact us at [support@roadmunk.com.](mailto:support@roadmunk.com?Subject=Support%20Case "Contact Support")

#### **Blogs**

Our website offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at [support@roadmunk.com](mailto:support@roadmunk.com?Subject=Support%20Case "Contact Support"). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information. If this is the case, we will let you know and indicate why.

#### **Security**

Roadmunk stresses its privacy and security standards. Although no one can guarantee absolute security, we regularly re-evaluate our privacy and security policies in order to adapt to new challenges. We follow generally accepted standards to protect the information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. We encrypt the most sensitive data that you store on Roadmunk using AWS EBS encryption that uses the AES-256 algorithm. All data in transit uses TLS 1.2.

#### **Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [support@roadmunk.com](mailto:support@roadmunk.com?Subject=Support%20Case "Contact Support"), or 130 Spadina Ave., Suite 500, Toronto, ON, M5V 2L4.

#### **Changes to our Privacy & Security Policy**

If we make a change to this privacy policy, we will provide you with notice (for example, by email, a sign-in notification, or some other means) prior to the change becoming effective. By continuing to use the Service after those changes become effective, you are agreeing to be bound by the revised Privacy and Security Policy; if you do not agree to the change, simply don't use the Service after the change is effective, in which case the change will not apply to you.
